tallstreet.com 2008-12-17

# Tall Street - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy 

Tall Street shares the privacy principles that [Wordpress](http://automattic.com/privacy/) have adopted 

Tall Street recognizes and empathizes with Internet users personal privacy concerns. Your privacy is critically important to us. At Tall Street we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services. 
  * We aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what’s visible to the public, seen by search engines, kept private, and permanently deleted.

Tall Street Inc. (“ **Tall Street** ”) operates [tallstreet.com](http://www.tallstreet.com/). It is Tall Street’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Tall Street collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Tall Street’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Tall Street’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Tall Street may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Tall Street also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Tall Street does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Tall Street’s websites choose to interact with Tall Street in ways that require Tall Street to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Tall Street gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for as a trader to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Tall Street. In this case, Tall Street collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Tall Street. Tall Street does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

Tall Street may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Tall Street may monitor click throughs on links or ratings to help identify spam. Tall Street may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Tall Street does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Tall Street discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Tall Street’s behalf or to provide services available at Tall Street’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Tall Street’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Tall Street will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Tall Street discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Tall Street believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Tall Street, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Tall Street website and have supplied your email address, Tall Street may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Tall Street and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Tall Street takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Tall Street does not employ the use of cookies for general searchers. Tall Street only employes the use cookies if you choose to be a trader, this to to identify them, their usage of Tall Street website, and their website access preferences. Tall Street visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Tall Street’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Tall Street’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Tall Street may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Tall Street’s sole discretion. Tall Street encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
